[music]
[Instructor] Alright so it's time
to get started working on Prototype 4.
Make sure to download
the starter Project files
in the link below
the video, and since
we've already done this
a couple of times,
I'll just open up my Project
inside of Unity.
Open up your Scenes Folder
in the Project window.
Open up your Prototype 4.
Delete your "SampleScene".
Now we have our next
Prototype set up.
Now you can see down
in the bottom here
we actually have a different
perspective on our Camera.
So if I select our Camera,
our "Projection" is currently
set to "Orthographic",
so it has a lot more
of a...
flatter look to it versus
that "Perspective View" that we have.
If you want your "Scene View"
to be the same
as your "Game View",
you can actually select
underneath the different
coordinates on the top-right
of the Scene view instead
of the Perspective View
which has this triangular cone shape
next to it.
We can select the "Isometric View",
which then gives us the 3 bars,
kind of a square shape.
And we can now see
our game just like it looks
in our Game View.
For now I'm going to just
keep it as perspective,
so it's easier to see,
where I place things for now.
And then in fact, you can run
the game right now.
So if you press the Play button,
you'll see all
of these cool Particle Effects
drifting in the Background
kind of like clouds in the sky.
Now we're ready to get started.
Alright.
So what you're going to do is open
up Unity Hub,
and create a Prototype 4
Project in your Course Directory.
Make sure to head to the link
below this video
to download the Project starter files,
and import them into your new
Unity Project.
Open up the Prototype 4 Scene,
and delete
the SampleScene without saving,
and then if you want to test
that you can click "Run"
to see the Particle Effects
in our Project.
So now it's your turn.
[music]